注：伯尔的外祖父即乔纳森·爱德华兹（Jonathan Edwards）神学家，美国宗教复兴运动“大觉醒运动”（The Great Awakening）领导人物著有步道词《落在忿怒上帝手中的罪人》（Sinners in the Hands of an Angry God）
我外公是传达上帝忿怒的牧师
My grandfather was A fire and brimstone preacher
牧师，牧师，牧师
Preacher, preacher, preacher
但生存之道无法全由布道揭示
But there are things that the homilies And hymns won't teach ya
揭示，揭示，揭示
Teach ya, teach ya, teach ya
-我母亲天赋异禀     -天赋异禀
-My mother was a genius     -Genius
注：伯尔的父亲、外祖父（爱德华兹）、母亲在1757-1758年，即伯尔两岁时，因患天花先后去世，父母去世中间仅相隔七个月
我父亲令人肃然起敬
My father commanded respect
肃然起敬，肃然起敬
Respect, respect
但他们突然过世，一言未留
When they died They left no instructions
家族赫赫名声，独靠我捍卫
Just a legacy to protect
死亡待谁都一样，不分低贱与高尚
Death doesn't discriminate Between the sinners and the saints
它若出击，猝不及防，势不可挡，但生活总要继续
It takes and it takes and it takes And we keep living anyway
世事无常，潮起潮退，我们会受挫崩溃，会犯错、后悔
We rise and we fall and we break And we make our mistakes